http://www.broadbandutopia.com/privacypolicy.html

Call Us:     1-469 955-17408am - 5pm CST Mon - Fri
Like us? Join us:
Structured Wiring Design ManualSolutions for wiring a homeWiring an OfficeRetail/Restaurant WiringDo it Yourself ResourcesStructured Wiring by the Sq FtConsulting ServicesCat5e and Cat6 Comparision
Structured WiringA/V Switching & ExtensionPremises WiringHome
AudioWall PlatesConnectorsVideo DistributionIP CamerasLighting ControlsOccupancy SensorsClearance Products
Bulk CableResidential Composite CableBulk Cat6 CableBulk Cat5e CableRG6 Coaxial CableIn-Wall Speaker Cablepatch cablesAudio Video Cables
Tools & TestersPaladin Structured Wiring Kit
Products by Manufacturer
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Testimonials
Search
Index
Info
Click to see Customer Ratings
Structured Wiring, Home Theater &
Office Networking Solutions.
Why buy parts when you can buy solutions. Pre-packaged home wiring kits available.
Start here for:  Structured Wiring Kits   Components   Cable
Eliminate patch panel mishaps/unhappy users with Levitons SecureRJ solutions.
Sound is 50% of the movie experience.
Get it all with our home theater wiring kits.What we do for:
IT Managers  SMBs  Corporate Sales  School & Government Sales
Home Owners  Installers  Electricians  DIYers  Builders  Resellers
About us            Safe shopping guarantee            Free Shipping
Augmented Cat6 (Cat6A) is here! Get speeds upto 10Gigabit (10,000 Mbps) on copper.
Start here for:   Cables, Patch panels & Connectors
Recessed power and low-voltage boxes for flat-panels and entertainment centers.
Start here for:
Solutions,
Retrofit Kit, TV box, Low voltage box
This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering
system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but
may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store
through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information
about your shopping experience. Please see the
Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more
information about how Yahoo! uses this information.Privacy Notice
At Broadband Utopia we are commited to providing you a high quality shopping experience and we respect your privacy. Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others.In order to process your order efficiently we will need to collect certain information from you. This information may include name, address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. Broadband Utopia does not share any of the financial information on your account with outside parties except as required to transact your orders.Broadband Utopia may periodically change this privacy policy and we ask that you revisit this page from time to time.Information Security Notice
BroadbandUtopia.com is hosted by a Yahoo server with the leading security technology in the industry. Your order with BroadbandUtopia.com is secure, which means that your personal information and credit card number are encrypted with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) security.
To further safeguard your privacy, credit card information stored on our servers is protected from unauthorized access and automatically deleted after 30 days.
